Hello hello everyone welcome back to my channel
today I am going to talk about a great
insurance company which has been
continuously making investors good money in the general insurance business since its
listing till now for the
long term if you
add it to your portfolio friends
then it can make you a lot of money
add an excellent company you will definitely make it
good money in your portfolio
after a good correction
now it is seeing a boom so
you can add it for the long term
friends so friends I am talking about the
legendary insurance company I am telling you
about ICICI Bank Insurance number eight a great company
in the insurance business how the stock traded on BSE NSE both Mahal
State eight times in August
let's see a great
rise of 2.25 percent in NSC a
rise of more than 28 rupees adjusted to win price
1377 previous to 1348 and today it is at 1355
this is the day Kalu in 1383
which is ICICI of Rs 1301 49
Lombard's Stark has created it, friends, it is a
giant company, you should establish it for the long
term. Let's check the return profile of IS,
how it has
earned returns for the investor. Today, a
rise of 2.13 percent was seen in the stock on BSE,
friends. In the past week, the stock has
earned a great return of 2.12%.
In one month, the stock was
seen gaining 9.34 percent. In 2019, a
decline of almost one percent was seen in the stock.
In one year, Stark has earned a return of about
nineteen and a half percent to its directors,
friends. Three year-
on-year data is not available. As you
know, it has not been that long for the stock list, so if you
give space to the giant company in the insurance sector for the long term, you will
definitely make good money. You
can see the volume around 1375 for the day after August 12.
Friends, after 342001, the city rates have been reached.
Take the 52-week target of ₹10 for Faisal stock.  805,
now
its 1440 has been seen, friends,
so it is a good company, give place for the long term,
good companies
can make you money in the long term, friends, or
you can see that it has
earned a return of 19 per cent in the last year, it
belongs to the insurance sector, the
market share is also quite good, 61 thousand 846,
this is a large cap company, so the
stock is always in the news and the
insurance sector is going to be India's next
batting tractor, friends, so
definitely include it in your portfolio
for the long term, if we
look at its holding pattern, the promoter has a holding of
51.8 per cent, in this he holds a great share of 26.61 per cent,
mutual funds hold 10.52
per cent, he
holds 7.4 per cent interest in non-institutional address
and if the holding of
3.5 per cent stake is seen in it, friends,
in ICICI General Insurance Law & Company, friends, the same majority stake
holder is the promoter, plus
waterhole England means mortgage inside the stock  There is
no problem in SEZ itself, it
is a completely debt free company, with the help of mutual fund, the
teams have taken 10.52% stake in it,
friends, the same FIR is that
in this, friends, 611 companies have
backed the holding of 26.61%, promoters with
IS holding ICICI Bank have
51.8% personal from the state, this is also a
private sector bank, as you know
this IS public shoulder is
with SBI chief through various skins, money is
invested in 2.08% voting of SBI,
we like you who have 5.72% stake in retail, it
is a great stock in general insurance room partner stock, if you give space for long term, it will
make you a lot of money,
if you invest money in big stocks for long term, then you can
become rich
friends soon